<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Services on Mulugeta 🖊 Partners | Africa Cosultants</title>
    <link>http://mulugeta.partners/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Services on Mulugeta 🖊 Partners | Africa Cosultants</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://mulugeta.partners/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Accounting</title>
      <link>http://mulugeta.partners/services/accounting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mulugeta.partners/services/accounting/</guid>
      <description>Financial accounting (or financial accountancy) is the field of accounting concerned with the summary, analysis and reporting of financial transactions related to a business.
Objectives Financial accounting and financial reporting are often used as synonyms.
 According to International Financial Reporting Standards: the objective of financial reporting is: To provide financial information that is useful to existing and potential investors, lenders and other creditors in making decisions about providing resources to the reporting entity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ethio-Bayern Chamber of Commerce</title>
      <link>http://mulugeta.partners/services/ebcc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mulugeta.partners/services/ebcc/</guid>
      <description>Bavaria is the debatably the strongest state in Germany in terms of economy. Various industries zare based in this state. World famous brands such as Mercedes and BMW are from Bavaria. Therefore, seeking flow of investment from Germany shall no doubt require attracting investment from the Bavaria state.
On the other hand, Ethiopia is largely liberalizing many of its sectors including telecom, power, banking and transport etc. Owing to predominant command economic structures that prevailed for almost half a century, the share the private sector in its economy is very limited.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Advisory</title>
      <link>http://mulugeta.partners/services/business-advisory/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mulugeta.partners/services/business-advisory/</guid>
      <description>Lorem markdownum, dictis umbrosum dextrum, Lelegeia quamquam distantes pares ignisque quaerit dederat gemino Aethiopesque caelo ulciscitur est. Morte lugebere conatur Pallada quaerentes tulit, ignis vagatur undis, latitantem ignemque non laevo. Terras seu favoni tectas movit hunc motuque damno tutoque quattuor. Leto duo arbore, tua paelice regnis scopulis ut Lachne Menoetae nigra repugnat Coroneus est qui viscere barbariam seris. Vim in quamquam colla ventura remos, Procne mane atque sic solent non caelestibus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Insights Incubator</title>
      <link>http://mulugeta.partners/services/insightsincubator/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mulugeta.partners/services/insightsincubator/</guid>
      <description>Insight Incubators (II) incubates and accelerates innovative ideas from different walks of life especially from young high school students, university students, university graduates and community, research institutions, government organizations, rural community.
Africa is the youngest continent in terms of age of its population. The case for Ethiopia, which is the 2nd most populated nation in the continent, is not different. More than 65% of its population is less than 35 years of age.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zege Coffee Roastery</title>
      <link>http://mulugeta.partners/services/zegecoffee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mulugeta.partners/services/zegecoffee/</guid>
      <description>Ethiopian coffee is one of the best coffees sold at premium price in the world market. However, the return from the sales does not necessarily get back to the actual growers, coffee traders and exporters.
This is due to absence of value addition in the coffee supply chain. The majority of Ethiopian coffee is being sold raw as green beans. Therefore, an immediate intervention is required in the coffee processing value chain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bavaria Import &amp; Export</title>
      <link>http://mulugeta.partners/services/importexport/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mulugeta.partners/services/importexport/</guid>
      <description>We import industrial products, machineries, electronic products etc from abroad to Ethiopia and export agricultural commodities such as coffee, pulses, grains, fresh produces such as fruits and vegetables, diary products, beef and honey using advanced innovative agricultural technologies (AgriTech).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Events and Logistics</title>
      <link>http://mulugeta.partners/services/logistics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mulugeta.partners/services/logistics/</guid>
      <description>Organization of technology and innovation focused events for employment and job creation, entrepreneurship and startups promotion, events that are targeted to promote international tour and travel to various tourist destinations in Ethiopia, business to business matching in different business sectors and industries.
We engage in arranging tour packages for tourists, air ticket and travel on different means of transportation as well as lodging and accommodation.
Our logistics solutions provide air and sea import and export supply chain and logistics services on different means of transportation, warehousing and storage facilities for dry, perishable and high value cargo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eco-Lodges, Resorts &amp; Real Estate</title>
      <link>http://mulugeta.partners/services/realestate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mulugeta.partners/services/realestate/</guid>
      <description>We engage in setting up climate smart conservation based eco-lodges in different parts of Ethiopia.
We also build and run cost effective resort facilities by applying innovative (ShelterTech) technology equipped inputs in lodging and overnighting destinations. Our facilities promote tourist information and guide facilities.
On the other hand, we develop real estates for multipurpose businesses and residence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Media Productions</title>
      <link>http://mulugeta.partners/services/media/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mulugeta.partners/services/media/</guid>
      <description>Our multimedia business focuses on production of high quality audio and video.
It makes use of technologically advanced production materials such as cameras, drones, recording and editing equipment. It aspires to promote different communities from different walks of life in Ethiopia. It unravels unexplored remote areas in Ethiopia and reaches destinations that have never been accessed before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Center of Excellence</title>
      <link>http://mulugeta.partners/services/leadership/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mulugeta.partners/services/leadership/</guid>
      <description>Our center of excellence offers specialized MBA in leading innovation and change, coaching mentorship and leadership, entrepreneurship and innovation, innovation leadership and consulting for middle level government technocrats, leaders of private businesses, corporate executives and university teachers in collaboration with University of Wurzburg. We apply up-to-date educational innovative technologies (EduTech).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Consultancy</title>
      <link>http://mulugeta.partners/services/consultancy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mulugeta.partners/services/consultancy/</guid>
      <description>We engage in providing principally in agriculture sector for government, smallholder farming, urban agriculture, dairy farming, poultry and bee keeping.
We also provide architecture and construction consultancy and advisory services for developers and contractors. We provide business and investment consultancy services for investors, corporations, businesses, individuals and corporations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Off-Grid Energy Solutions</title>
      <link>http://mulugeta.partners/services/energy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mulugeta.partners/services/energy/</guid>
      <description>We attract international investors from Germany and Europe in general to engage in off-grid energy solutions such as small scale wind turbines, solar panels, geothermal energy, ethanol production and biogas energy alternatives for rural and remote locations in Ethiopia.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>